{"data":[{"question":"We don't know what ___ really said. It all ___ strange to us.","a":"are, sound","b":"is, sound","c":"are, sounds","d":"was, sounds","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Sometimes the pronoun who, that, or which is the subject of a verb in the middle of the sentence. The pronouns who, that, and which become singular or plural according to the noun directly in front of them \n- It all: subject is \"it\" which is singular","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Your daughter has three children, hasn't she? \"Yes, she ___\"","a":"was married to be young","b":"was married young","c":"married to be young","d":"married young","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Active voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"A wooden building can easily ___ fire.","a":"spread","b":"reach","c":"catch","d":"burn","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Catch: if something catches fire, it starts to burn accidentally","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Jeff ___ his letter into the postbox.","a":"fell","b":"dropped","c":"dropped","d":"threw","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Drop sth into: to take something to a place and leave it there","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"As the theater was still closed, I went window-shopping to ___ time.","a":"use","b":"kill","c":"spend","d":"take","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Kill time: to spend time doing something which is not important while you are waiting to do something important or waiting for something else to happen","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"The writer living opposite door is known ___ the public.","a":"to","b":"with","c":"of","d":"by","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Known to the public: famous to public","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Beatrice ___ Harry for ten years.","a":"married with","b":"married","c":"has been married to","d":"has been marrying","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense \n- Be married to someone","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Rose wondered if she looked as funny to Wendy as Wendy ___ to her.","a":"did","b":"does","c":"did it","d":"looks","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Did it= Looked as funny","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"You look happy today, Steven. \"I like my new suit and dad _________, too.\"","a":"likes","b":"does","c":"do","d":"is","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Use an auxiliary verb when you want to avoid repeating some part of your sentence (because it can be deduced from the context) \n- Dad does= dad likes","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Here ___ the bus! Hurry up!","a":"come","b":"is coming","c":"has come","d":"comes","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The words here and there have generally been labeled as adverbs even though they indicate place. In sentences beginning with here or there, the subject follows the verb \n+The bus: singular","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"}]}